I've been thinking a lot about this
experience of
reading a transcript actually of one of
the the dialogues I did with them with
John Becky and Jordan Hall and
Christopher and we're all working on
this anthology together this you're all
contributing a section to this and
basically about dialogue dialogue OHS
and in the chapter that Chris and John
are writing part of the part of it was
was you know laying out the transcript
of one of the dialogues and and I read
it and Chris read it and Chris mentioned
something that was really striking
because it was really my experience too
which was in reading them in reading the
text it was so clear how world forming
the conversation was
like there really was a sense in which
reading it you can really kind of get
this world start formed and in some way
the world it became so obvious that the
world were the ones who were coming to
character as the inter lockers in a way
that wasn't as a parent when we were in
the dialogue and it's not what I'm not
saying is it wasn't like being in the
dialogue
I mean clearly there was a world being
through that conversation was world ik
but it wasn't foreground in fact I would
it's also kind of seems obvious you know
reading it is that you know because this
is what a world does right it it becomes
the background or the horizon that
allows the particulars of that world to
gather right and in its withdrawal the
world as such the particular world of
the fruit fly or the sidewalk or the
person walking down the sidewalk that
gets to come into appearance until in
some sense right the the world form a
formation of the conversation was a
world of the degree that did withdrawal
however in what was foreground for us
were the particular people right the
faces of the other and what they said
and being one of the people
and there really is this this awareness
and this is part of what makes it dialo
gose is that on some level there is a
sense in which you hear yourself putting
together thoughts in such a way insane
things spontaneously that are so above
your normal pay grade right and that's
the fascinating part of it right
so
and I think what well what's interesting
about being one of the inner lockers is
that where I do think the background or
the world bled into the foreground I
think is as is in the experience of a
profound affinity felt with each other
there's a certain kind of sparkling
glistening sense of kind of I don't know
what what to call it just other than a
stunning almost transpersonal affinity
for the other it's clearly quite
ecstatic and I think I think that's
those those moments of affinity are the
way that the world breaks through right
becomes it bleeds through the figure and
one could say that you know the
conversation was this kind of background
foreground background foreground right
world forming
you know I suppose what we can say I
noticed seeing that that one will one
begins to wonder the particular
character one is in your life kind of
seems it seems like you're the person
I'm the one walking of the one talking
I'm in the world but I wonder I wonder
if it isn't also the case that the
characters that we become are as such as
being a part of a conversation that in
itself is world forming and that world
is coming into character